

CONTACT ME AT

- Address: Jl. Keselamatan no 3, Tebet ,South Jakarta , DKI Jakarta , Indonesia 12860
- Rininovianti171015@gmail.com
- +62-85703634001
- @Rini.noviantiii

SKILLS SUMMARY

- • Cooperate
- Programming Java, C++,
 Phyton
- •••• Ms. Office applications
- Data analysis and problem solving
- ••• Networking and Multimedia
- •••• Public Speaking
- ••• General Knowledge

AWARDS RECEIVED

- Short Story Writing for the Asian English Olympics in (2021)
- The top 10 best business competition proposals, Energy Academy Indonesia (2020)
- The top 5 ITB Urban Motion Competition Essay, (2017)

RINI NOVIANTI

TELECOMMUNICATION ENGINEERING COLLEGE STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a telecommunications engineering student at the Academy Telkom Jakarta . I am able to develop my skills and knowledge in programming, networking and multimedia design. I have the ability to speak well, able to apply the material that has been conveyed well, and I am the person responsible for solving problems

WORK EXPERIENCE

Laboratory Assistant

Academy Telkom Jakarta | Oct 2020 - Present

- Conducts teaching theory, circuits, arrangements, and calculations on applied physics and electronics
- Create work performance and technical functional documents

Backlink Website

Academy Telkom Jakarta | April 2021 - Present

- manage data and website and enter data to increase website flexibility
- create a data analysis document in the form of a link
- Analyze the progress of the increase in the appearance of the website

EXPERIENCE IN ORGANIZATION

Meet in The After Mitam Gathering

Public Marketing and Documentation | Mei 2016 - August 2016

Actively participate in the Organization at the Academy Telkom Jakarta

 Has joined the Electrical Student Association and has participated in several other student activity unit programs such as the Choir, Akatel English Club, and SONIC

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Akademi Telkom Jakarta A.Md | 2019-2022

 Academy Telkom Jakarta has given the student a lot of CISCO material like networking, and other things such as programming as well. Determined and scheduled priorities as required to progress engineering works